# MOFFAT KANIARU

# AUTOMOTIVE PARTS MANAGER

#### CONTACT

+254727918291

 $\boxtimes$ 

moffatkaniaru@gmail.com



Nairobi, KEN



linkedin.com/in/moffat-mbugua-99a63618a

#### SKILLS

Employee Management
Inventory Management
Customer Service Management
Customer Retention Management
Operations Oversight
Logistics
Data Management
Basic HTML, CSS & JavaScript

## EDUCATION

**Animal Production & Health Management** 

# YMCA College Of Agriculture & Technology

2017-2019

**Animal Nutrition** 

**High School Diploma** 

### Kairi High School

2012-2016

GED

\_\_\_\_\_

#### LANGUAGES

English

Native

German

Elementary Proficiency

Swahili

Native

#### PROFILE

Encouraging manager with 5 years+ experience, analytical problem solver with talents for team building, leading and motivating, as well as excellent customer relations aptitude and relationship building skills, Proficient in using independent decision making skills and sound judgment to positively impact company success.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Part Store Manager**

JK Automotive Parts Store & Service Center

1/2020-present

- Maximized to sales growth by up selling product and Services based on individual customer requirements by 67%.
- Aligned 13 employees for shifts, taking into account100% customer traffic and employee strength.
- Expedited escalated calls efficiently, finding satisfactory resolutions for both customers and company alike.
- Coordinated customer support and shop administration

Contact: Mary Mbugua - nyathirakaniaru@gmail.com

#### **Animal Nutritionist**

12/2018-12/2019

Pembe Flour Mills Ltd

- Integrated animal nutrition and feed based solutions to enhance livestock productivity through the adoption of new technologies.
- Consolidated customer retention by creating and offering unique and inspiring interest in new product lines with the first 4 months of employment.
- Conducted regular reviews of operations and identified areas of improvement.

Contact: Marjan Mohammed - marjan@pembe.co.ke

### Farm Manager

1/2017-1/2018

**Humste Farm Estates** 

- Enhanced use of local feed including pasture and suitable agro-industrial byproducts and explore novel and use alternative feed.
- Demonstrated strong organizational and time management skills while managing multiple projects
- Inspected and repaired equipment for livestock and crop management.
- Developed advanced understanding of farm operations Purchasing needs and labor requirements.

Contact: John Kariuki - kaniarujohn@gmail.com